Guide to the Norton Nicholls Correspondence
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1750 Jun 27
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Bern. Concerns Thomas Gray; Bern, Switzerland, 1771 Sep 29 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - George Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Ditchley Park. Concerns Norton Nicholls, 1771 Sep 30 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Chiavenna. Concerns Bern, Switzerland, 1771 Oct 2 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Milan. Concerns family business; Italy; Milanese court, 1771 Oct 18 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Yverdun., 1771 Oct 22 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Bern. Concerns Norton Nicholls; Italy, 1771 [Nov] (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Bern., 1771 [Nov] (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Bern. Concerns Florentine court, [1771 Nov 4] (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - B. Tscharner to Norton Nicholls. Aubonne. Concerns Florentine court, 1771 Nov 9 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Milan. Concerns Italy, 1771 Dec 10 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - George Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Ditchleys. Concerns Norton Nicholls, 1771 Dec 15 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Milan. Concerns Milanese court; music, 1771 Dec 24 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Milan. Concerns Milanese court; Thomas Gray; Count Charles Firmian, 1772 Jan 24 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Milan. Concerns Count Charles Firmian; Horace Mann, 1772 Feb 8 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Milan. Concerns Milanese court; Count Charles Firmian, 1772 Feb 9 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Bern. Concerns Bern, Switzerland; Norton Nicholls, [1772] Feb 10 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Bologna. Concerns Italy; mention of a travel journal of NN, 1772 Mar 7 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Ipolito Salviati Caprara to Norton Nicholls. Bologna., 1772 Mar 14 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Count Wilseck to Norton Nicholls. Florence., [1772] Mar 17 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Mary Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Ditchleys. Concerns family, 1772 Mar 16 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Florence. Concerns Horace Mann; Ipolito Salviati Caprara; Count Wilseck, 1772 Mar 21 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Marie Morasini Belcredi to Norton Nicholls. Milan., 1772 Apr 6 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Ipolito Salviati Caprara to John Minifie. Bologna., 1772 Apr 7 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Count Wilseck to Norton Nicholls. Florence. Concerns Florentine court, 1772 Apr 17 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Duchess di Castelpagano to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns her co-author Wurmbrand, 1772 May 26 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Rome. Concerns Italy, 1772 May 6 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Rome. Concerns John Spurgeon; Italy, 1772 May 19 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Milanese court, 1772 May 26 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Milanese court; Norton Nicholls, 1772 May 30 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Count Charles Firmian to Norton Nicholls. Milan. Concerns Count Wilseck, 1772 Jun 3 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Naples. Concerns Italy, 1772 Jun 12 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Duchess di Castelpagano to Norton Nicholls. Naples., [1772] (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Duchess di Castelpagano to Norton Nicholls. Naples. Concerns Italy; her co-author Wurmbrand, [1772] (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Wurmbrand to Norton Nicholls. Naples., [1772] (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Duchess di Castelpagano to Norton Nicholls. Naples. Concerns Wurmbrand, [1772] (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Unidentified to Norton Nicholls. n.p., 1772 Jun (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Milanese court; Count Charles Firmian, 1772 Jun 29 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Naples. Concerns Italy, 1772 Jun 30 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Naples. Concerns Italy, 1772 Jul 14 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Naples. Concerns Italy, 1772 Jul 21 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns Cambridge University; Norton Nicholls, 1772 Aug 1 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Ipolito Salviati Caprara to Norton Nicholls. Capove., 1772 Aug 8 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Leopoldina Stahremburg to Norton Nicholls. Florence. Concerns Count Wilseck, 1772 Aug 11 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Unidentified to Norton Nicholls. Naples., 1772 Aug 11 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Milanese court, 1772 Aug 13 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Duchess di Castelpagano to Norton Nicholls. Naples., 1772 Aug 14 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Princess Castiglione to Norton Nicholls. Naples. Concerns Italy, 1772 Aug 15 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Duchess di Castelpagano to Norton Nicholls. Naples. Count Charles Firmian; Wurmbrand, [1772] (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Duchess di Castelpagano to Norton Nicholls. Naples., [1772] (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Unidentified to unidentified. n.p., n.d. (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Rome. Concerns Italy; family, 1772 Sep 5 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Duchess di Castelpagano to Norton Nicholls. Naples., 1772 Sep 1 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Rome. Concerns Italy; Roman Catholicism, 1772 Sep 19 (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - Duchess di Castelpagano to Norton Nicholls. Naples. Concerns Italy; Wurmbrand, 1772 Sep 30 (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Bologna. Concerns Norton Nicholls; mention of planned journals, 1772 Oct 17 (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Venice. Concerns Italy, 1772 Nov 11 (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - W. Gibson to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns William Mason, 1773 Nov 24 [sic] (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - Leopoldina Stahremberg to Norton Nicholls. Florence. Concerns Count Wilseck; Florentine court. Same letter as 179 (inside out), 1772 Nov 24 (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - Wilseck to Countess Stahremberg. Florence. See 178, 1772 Nov 24 (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Milan. Concerns John Minifie; Italy, 1772 Dec 1 (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Bern., 1772 Dec 12 (Box 2, Folder 181)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Milan. Concerns Count Charles Firmian; Milanese court; Thomas Gray, 1772 Dec 15 (Box 2, Folder 182)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Milan. Concerns Milanese court, 1772 Dec 19 (Box 2, Folder 183)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Concerns Milan; Milanese court, 1772 Dec 23 (Box 2, Folder 184)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Marseilles. Concerns Marseilles; France, 1773 Jan 11 (Box 2, Folder 185)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Marseilles. Concerns Marseilles; France, 1773 Jan 14 (Box 2, Folder 186)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Aix. Concerns France, 1773 Jan 18 (Box 2, Folder 187)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Avignon. Concerns France, 1773 Feb 1 (Box 2, Folder 188)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lyons. Concerns France, 1773 Feb 9 (Box 2, Folder 189)
  - Crillon de Brences to Norton Nicholls. Avignon. Concerns Norton Nicholls, 1773 Feb 19 (Box 2, Folder 190)
  - Unidentified to unidentified. n.p., n.d. (Box 2, Folder 191)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. n.p. Concerns Versailles; France, 1773 Mar 8 (Box 2, Folder 192)
  - Countess Stahremberg to Norton Nicholls. Florence. Concerns Count Wilseck; Florentine court, 1773 Mar 30 (Box 2, Folder 193)
  - Leopoldina Stahremberg to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns Florence; Count Wilseck, [1773] (Box 2, Folder 194)
  - Leopoldina Stahremberg to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns Florence, [1773] (Box 2, Folder 195)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Bern. Concerns B. Tscharner; Cambridge University, 1773 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 196)
  - Leopoldina Stahremberg to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns Florence, 1773 May 14 (Box 2, Folder 197)
  - Leopoldina Stahremberg to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns Florence; Wurmbrand; Countess Stahremberg, 1773 Jun 8 (Box 2, Folder 198)
  - -- Kunigl to Norton Nicholls. Milan. Concerns Count Wilseck; Count Charles Firmian, 1773 Jul 4 (Box 2, Folder 199)
  - B. Tscharner to Norton Nicholls. Aubonne., 1773 Jul 24 (Box 2, Folder 200)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Milan; -- Kunigl; Wurmbrand, 1773 Jul 19 (Box 2, Folder 201)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Milanese court. Includes copy of letter by Voltaire "on his death bed", 1773 Jul 29 (Box 2, Folder 202)
  - Countess Stahremberg to Norton Nicholls. Florence. Concerns Florentine court, 1773 Sep 4 (Box 2, Folder 203)
  - Baglion du Prouse to Norton Nicholls. Louville., 1773 Sep 22 (Box 2, Folder 204)
  - Su[san] Turner to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Putney. Concerns family, 1773 Sep 28 (Box 2, Folder 205)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Milanese court, 1773 Oct 15 (Box 2, Folder 206)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Valegres. Concerns B. Tscharner; William Mason, 1773 Nov 1 (Box 2, Folder 207)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Milanese court; Count Charles Firmian, 1773 Dec 9 (Box 2, Folder 208)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Milan. Concerns Milanese court, 1773 Dec 12 (Box 2, Folder 209)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London; Indian affairs, 1773 (Box 2, Folder 210)
  - Countess Stahremberg to Norton Nicholls. Florence. Concerns Milanese court, 1773 Dec 14 (Box 2, Folder 211)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Milan. Concerns Kunigl, 1773 Dec 20 (Box 2, Folder 212)
  - [Count Wilseck?] to Norton Nicholls. Naples., 1774 Jan 4 (Box 2, Folder 213)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Ditchleys. Concerns family; gardening, 1774 Apr 7 (Box 2, Folder 214)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Bern., 1774 Apr 26 (Box 2, Folder 215)
  - E. Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Ditchleys. Concerns family, 1774 Apr 28 (Box 2, Folder 216)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family, 1774 Apr 30 (Box 2, Folder 217)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Ditchleys. Concerns family health; Augustus Floyer, 1774 May 11 (Box 2, Folder 218)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Scotland; Charles de Bonstetten; Milanese court, 1774 May 29 (Box 2, Folder 219)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Alloa House. Concerns Scotland; John Erskine, 1774 Jul 10 (Box 2, Folder 220)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Alloa House. Concerns Scotland; John Erskine, 1774 Jul 15 (Box 2, Folder 221)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Alloa House. Concerns Scotland; family; Indian affairs, 1774 Jul 22 (Box 2, Folder 222)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Florence. Concerns Count Wilseck, 1774 Jul 23 (Box 2, Folder 223)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Alloa House. Concerns Scotland, 1774 Jul 29 (Box 2, Folder 224)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Alloa House. Concerns Scotland, 1774 Aug 2 (Box 2, Folder 225)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Edinburgh. Concerns Scotland, [1774] Aug 9 (Box 2, Folder 226)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Alloa House. Concerns Scotland, 1774 Aug 24 (Box 2, Folder 227)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Alloa House. Concerns Scotland, 1774 Aug 25 (Box 2, Folder 228)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Milanese court, 1774 Sep 1 (Box 2, Folder 229)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Alloa House., 1774 Sep 3 (Box 2, Folder 230)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1774 Sep 15 (Box 2, Folder 231)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Bern. Concerns Milanese court; Count Charles Firmian; Kunigl, 1774 Nov 26 (Box 2, Folder 232)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Milanese court, 1775 Feb 9 (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. Paris. Concerns France, 1775 May 20 (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Richmond., 1775 Jul 5 (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cossey., 1775 Aug 3 (Box 3, Folder 236)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cossey. Concerns advowson, 1775 Aug 7 (Box 3, Folder 237)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cossey., 1775 Aug 13 (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - B. Tscharner to Norton Nicholls. Aubonne. Concerns Charles de Bonstetten, 1775 Aug 25 (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Ditchleys. Concerns family, 1776 Jul 3 (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Richmond., 1776 Jul 13 (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Richmond. Concerns family business, 1776 Aug 4 (Box 3, Folder 242)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Richmond. Concerns Thomas Gray, 1776 Aug 11 (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee. Concerns advowson, 1776 Aug 18 (Box 3, Folder 244)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee. Concerns Charles de Bonstetten, 1776 Aug 27 (Box 3, Folder 245)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Lee. Concerns family business, 1776 Sep 3 (Box 3, Folder 246)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Milanese court; Thomas Gray, 1776 Sep 28 (Box 3, Folder 247)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Milanese court; Count Charles Firmian; American Revolution, 1776 Dec 1 (Box 3, Folder 248)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo., 1777 Apr 15 (Box 3, Folder 249)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London., 1777 Jun 17 (Box 3, Folder 250)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cossey., 1777 Jul 5 (Box 3, Folder 251)
  - Frances Allen to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family business, [1777] (Box 3, Folder 252)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Count Wilseck; American Revolution, 1777 Jul 29 (Box 3, Folder 253)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns American Revolution; Milanese court, 1777 Sep 27 (Box 3, Folder 254)
  - Jane Floyer Nicholls to Whichcott Turner. Blundeston. Concerns Norton Nicholls, 1777 Oct 7 (Box 3, Folder 255)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Valegres. Concerns B. Tscharner; Thomas Gray, 1777 Oct 9 (Box 3, Folder 256)
  - Whichcott Turner to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Richmond. Reply to 255, 1777 Oct 14 (Box 3, Folder 257)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Milanese court, 1777 Nov 4 (Box 3, Folder 258)
  - W. J[erningham] to Norton Nicholls. Rome. Concerns Italy; Count Wilseck, 1778 Jan 24 (Box 3, Folder 259)
  - J. F. Erskine to Norton Nicholls. Alloa House. Concerns family business, 1778 Feb 1 (Box 3, Folder 260)
  - J. F. Erskine to Norton Nicholls. Alloa House. Concerns family business, 1778 Feb 1 (Box 3, Folder 261)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Maltby. Concerns Cambridge University; family business, 1778 Mar 7 (Box 3, Folder 262)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Maltby. Concerns family, 1778 Mar 22 (Box 3, Folder 263)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Maltby., 1778 Apr 21 (Box 3, Folder 264)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1778 Jun 27 (Box 3, Folder 265)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1778 Jun 30 (Box 3, Folder 266)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Richmond. Concerns Indian affairs, 1778 Jul 7 (Box 3, Folder 267)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Ditchleys. Concerns music, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 268)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Milanese court; American Revolution, 1778 Dec 1 (Box 3, Folder 269)
  - Charles de Bonstetten to Norton Nicholls. Rome. Concerns Italy, 1779 Feb 15 (Box 3, Folder 270)
  - Teresa Monti to Norton Nicholls. Turin., 1779 Jul 8 (Box 3, Folder 271)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family; American Revolution, 1779 Jul 18 (Box 3, Folder 272)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns family business; James Ogilvy, Earl of Findlater, [1779 Jul] (Box 3, Folder 273)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Biggleswade. Concerns James Ogilvy, Earl of Findlater, 1779 Aug 5 (Box 3, Folder 274)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Edinburgh. Concerns Scotland, 1779 Aug 18 (Box 3, Folder 275)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House., 1779 Sep 5 (Box 3, Folder 276)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Banff. Concerns James Ogilvy, Earl of Findlater; J. F. Erskine, 1779 Sep 12 (Box 3, Folder 277)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House., 1779 Oct 6 (Box 3, Folder 278)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House. Concerns James Ogilvy, Earl of Findlater; Alexander Gordon, Duke of Gordon, 1779 Oct 17 (Box 3, Folder 279)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House., 1779 Oct 29 (Box 3, Folder 280)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House. Concerns family business, 1779 Nov 7 (Box 3, Folder 281)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House. Concerns family business, 1779 Nov 12 (Box 3, Folder 282)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House., 1779 Nov 21 (Box 3, Folder 283)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House. Concerns Alexander Gordon, Duke of Gordon; family business, 1779 Dec 1 (Box 3, Folder 284)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House. Concerns family business, 1779 Dec 10 (Box 3, Folder 285)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House. Concerns Alexander Gordon, Duke of Gordon, 1779 Dec 20 (Box 3, Folder 286)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Trezzo. Concerns Milanese court; Italy, 1779 Dec 25 (Box 3, Folder 287)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House., 1779 Dec 29 (Box 3, Folder 288)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House. Concerns family business, 1780 Jan 5 (Box 3, Folder 289)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House. Concerns family, 1780 Jan 14 (Box 3, Folder 290)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House. Concerns advowson; Indian affairs, 1780 Jan 19 (Box 3, Folder 291)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House. Concerns Augustus Floyer; James Ogilvy, Earl of Findlater, 1780 Jan 28 (Box 3, Folder 292)
  - Norton Nicholls to Lady Caroline Findlater. Cullen House., [1780] (Box 3, Folder 293)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House., 1780 Feb 6 (Box 3, Folder 294)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House., 1780 Feb 15 (Box 3, Folder 295)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House. Concerns sermons; gardening, 1780 Feb 27 (Box 3, Folder 296)
  - T. Gordon to Norton Nicholls. Gordon Castle. Concerns Norton Nicholls, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 297)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Gordon Castle. Concerns gardening, 1780 Mar 26 (Box 3, Folder 298)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House. Concerns family, 1780 Mar 29 (Box 3, Folder 299)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House. Concerns family business, 1780 Apr 7 (Box 3, Folder 300)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House. Concerns James Ogilvy, Earl of Findlater; sermons, 1780 Apr 16 (Box 3, Folder 301)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House. Concerns John Minifie, 1780 Apr 26 (Box 3, Folder 302)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Cullen House. Concerns Scotland, 1780 May 31 (Box 3, Folder 303)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Alloa. Concerns Scotland; Augustus Floyer, 1780 July 26 (Box 3, Folder 304)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Alloa. Concerns J. F. Erskine; music, 1780 July 31 (Box 3, Folder 305)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Alloa. Concerns gardening; Scotland, 1780 Aug 8 (Box 3, Folder 306)
  - Lady Caroline Findlater to Norton Nicholls. Cullen House., [1780] Aug 29 (Box 3, Folder 307)
  - Lady Caroline Findlater to Norton Nicholls. Edinburgh. Continuation of 307, [1780] Aug 29 (Box 3, Folder 308)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Alloa. Concerns music, 1780 Sep 15 (Box 3, Folder 309)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Copgrove. Concerns Thomas Gray; William Mason, 1780 Oct 13 (Box 3, Folder 310)
  - Elisabel Mille to Norton Nicholls. n.p., 1780 Nov 12 (Box 3, Folder 311)
  - Lady Caroline Findlater to Norton Nicholls. Edinburgh. Concerns Scotland, 1781 Jan 19 (Box 3, Folder 312)
  - James Ogilvy, Duke of Findlater to Norton Nicholls. Edinburgh. Concerns Scotland (Box 3, Folder 313)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Pisa. Concerns Milanese court; Count Wilseck, 1781 Mar 5 (Box 3, Folder 314)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Malines. Concerns Emperor Joseph II, 1781 July 4 (Box 3, Folder 315)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Malines. Concerns Emperor Joseph II; literature; Roman Catholicism, 1781 Aug 26 (Box 3, Folder 316)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Beccles., [1781 Sep 13] (Box 3, Folder 317)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Malines. Concerns Emperor Joseph II, 1781 Sep 21 (Box 3, Folder 318)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Malines. Concerns Roman Catholicism; Emperor Joseph II, 1781 Oct 25 (Box 3, Folder 319)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Malines. Concerns Emperor Joseph II; American Revolution; James Ogilvy, Earl of Findlater, 1781 Dec 21 (Box 3, Folder 320)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Kimbolton Castle., [1782 Jan 7] (Box 3, Folder 321)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Malines. Concerns Emperor Joseph II; Parliament, 1782 Apr 2 (Box 3, Folder 322)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Parliament, [1782] Apr 15 (Box 3, Folder 323)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns Emperor Joseph II; Count Charles Firmian, 1782 Apr 8 (Box 3, Folder 324)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns London, 1782 Apr 21 (Box 3, Folder 325)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns music, 1782 Apr 30 (Box 3, Folder 326)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Malines. Concerns John Minifie; Emperor Joseph II, 1782 Apr 30 (Box 3, Folder 327)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns Parliament, 1782 May 9 (Box 3, Folder 328)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns Parliament, 1782 May 28 (Box 3, Folder 329)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Malines. Concerns Count Charles Firmian; clergy, 1782 June 1 (Box 3, Folder 330)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns clergy, 1782 June 15 (Box 3, Folder 331)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. Concerns Lee, 1782 June 26 (Box 3, Folder 332)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Malines. Concerns Count Charles Firmian; clergy; Emperor Joseph II, 1782 July 18 (Box 3, Folder 333)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London. Concerns Sir Horace Mann, 1782 Jul 19 (Box 3, Folder 334)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. Concerns London., 1782 Aug 5 (Box 3, Folder 335)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. Concerns London; sermons, 1782 Aug 13 (Box 3, Folder 336)
  - Norton Nicholls to Jane Floyer Nicholls. London., 1782 Aug 10 (Box 3, Folder 337)
  - John Wheler to Norton Nicholls. Concerns London; sermons, 1782 [Aug] (Box 3, Folder 338)
  - John Minifie to Norton Nicholls. Malines. Concerns Count Wilseck, 1782 Sep 15 (Box 3, Folder 339)